lyte.com 2018-08-31

# Lyte

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) of Lyte, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“Lyte” or “we” or “us”), describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide to us via the lyte.com website or any other website owned or operated by us (collectively, the “Site”) or the Lyte e-ticket selling or ticket purchasing service or any other service accessed through the Site (collectively, the “Service”). Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to the Site or the Service.

#### What information do we collect?

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, mobile device type, mobile device ID, language preference, referring site, date and time of each visitor request, duration of use, and information about the way our visitors use and navigate through the Site and the Service. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our websites and services, and to optimize the Site and the Service. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We only disclose logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information as described below. Depending on how visitors to the Site choose to interact with us, we may also gather additional personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, in order to request a quote for an electronic ticket (a “Ticket”), you must submit the Ticket to us, including the information set forth on the Ticket, which may include the ticketholder's name, address and other information. In order to receive the purchase price for a Ticket we have purchased from you, or to pay for a Ticket you have purchased from us, you must register through our application to establish an account with us and provide personal and financial information required to process the transaction. You may also provide us with information when you contact us for help or additional information. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of your interaction with us. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the Site. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### What do we use your information for?

We may use any the information we collect from you in one or more of the following ways:

  * To provide you with information about the Service or changes to the Site or the Service 
  * To respond to your inquiries
  * To process transactions
  * To improve the Site
  * To improve customer service 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature
  * To send periodic emails

We may use non-personally identifiable information for marketing or advertising purposes.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future promotional emails from us, you can do so at any time simply by using an email's unsubscribe function.

#### How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied financial or other sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database, where it is accessible only to those who are authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

After a purchase transaction, we retain your financial information as long as it is necessary and relevant for our operations. In addition, we may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with the law, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, or assist with any investigation.

#### To whom do we disclose your information?

We disclose personally-identifying and non-personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors, service providers (who are under contract to help with our business operations, such as fraud detection, payment processing and other services), and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide the Service, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, service providers and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

In addition, we may disclose personally-identifying and non-personally-identifying information (but excluding financial information) ) collected by us when you use of the Service to request information about Tickets available for purchase, to place reservations to purchase Tickets, or to purchase or sell Tickets to the related event, to artists, artist managers, event organizers and event promoters that have requested such information to artists, artist managers, event organizers and event promoters that have requested such information and that have agreed not to disclose the information to others. Artists, artist managers, event organizers and event promoters may use your information to provide you with updates about the related event, for marketing or advertising purposes, and for other purposes. We do not control the privacy policies of artists, artist managers, event organizers and event promoters, and you are subject to the privacy policies of such third parties where applicable.

In order for us to sell a Ticket we have purchased from you, we disclose at a minimum the information set forth on the Ticket to the third-party purchaser or third-party service providers that facilitate the sale of the Ticket. We may also disclose to such third parties additional personally-identifying information, but only to the extent necessary to complete such sale. We do not control the privacy policies of such third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of such third parties where applicable.

Other than to our employees, contractors, service providers affiliated organizations, third-party purchasers, and third-party service providers, and artists, artist managers, event organizers and event promoters as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property or rights, or the property or rights of third parties or the public at large; or to investigate fraud. We may provide non-personally identifiable information to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the parties to whom we disclose any personal information use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy; however, Lyte is not liable for the use of this information by those parties.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the Site, and their website access preferences. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you should set your browser to refuse cookies before using the Site, with the caveat that certain features of the Site may not function properly without the aid of cookies

#### Registration and Sharing Through Third-Party Services

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties such as Facebook or other social media sites. The information we have access to varies by site and is controlled by your privacy settings on that site and your authorization. By associating an account managed by a third party with your account with us and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Business Transfers

If we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. The Site and the Service are directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

#### Privacy Shield

We participate in and comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework principals as documented [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personally identifiable information. The list of participating organizations can be found [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, Lyte is subject to the investigatory and enforcement authority of the US Federal Trade Commission.

#### Privacy Shield: Access Rights

You may have the right to access, edit, or delete the personal data you have provided to us by sending a written request to the contact address provided below. In some cases, these access rights may not apply, if the requests are unreasonably burdensome or expensive, in the sole judgement of Lyte. We may request specific personal information in order to confirm your identity and protect our other customers, prior to addressing any requests under this section.

#### Privacy Shield: Your Choices

You may choose to change your personal data or to cancel your account by contacting us using the information provided below. You may opt-out of our marketing communications using the unsubscribe buttons provided in the messages.

#### Privacy Shield: Onward Transfer

We try to minimize disclosures of personal data as reasonably practical because we are mindful of our responsibility and potential liability in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

#### Privacy Shield Recourse Mechanism

Our independent recourse mechanism for any disputes related to Privacy Shield is [JAMS](https://www.jamsadr.com/). In the event that your Privacy Shield dispute cannot be solved first through our support team and second through dispute resolutions via JAMS, you have the right to invoke binding arbitration via the Privacy Shield Panel, which has the authority to impose individual-specific, non-monetary equitable relief (such as access, correction, deletion, or return of the data in question). No damages, costs, fees, or other remedies are available and each party shall bear its own attorney's fees.

#### Contact Us

For any inquiries about our privacy policy, usage of data, to update or access your data, or any other matter, please email us at [support@lyte.com](mailto:support@lyte.com).

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Site.
